Tomoyuki Fujii

Full-stack developer

LinkedIn: Tomoyuki Fujii / GitHub: Tomoyuki 3001 / Portfolio: Tomoyuki Fujii

Summary

Junior Full-stack Developer with 2 years of experience in web development and a passion for user experience and interaction design and strength in creative and strategic thinking. Learning and growing as a developer are important to me and I am excellent at working in teams and enjoy collaboration.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, MySQL, MongoDB, GitHub

Education

Cornerstone International Community College | January 2022 ~ December 2022 Web development diploma

Tokai University | April 2014 ~ March 2018Bachelor of Political Science and Economics

Employment

Tellext Inc. Vancouver, Canada | March 2023 ~Present

Full-stack developer

- Improved code quality through code reviews, bug fixes, and optimizations.
- Led modern website development using WordPress, HTML, and CSS.
- Optimized databases with AWS for improved data organization and accessibility.
- Boosted website loading speed by 20% through optimization techniques.
- Leading cutting-edge application development with TypeScript and Next.js for security robot control.
- Collaborated with a team of 15 to exceed client expectations.

Dunlop Sports Marketing Ltd. Tokyo, **Japan | April 2018 ~ June 2021** Sales Representative

- Customer information and budget management.
- Create proposals to acquire new clients and increase sales of existing clients.

Projects

A school website - Skills: React.js, Node.js, Postgres Website / GitHub
Students and instructors can see their own profile page, make new appointments, and make their own schedule with a booking system.

A social media app - Skills: React.js, Node.js Website / GitHub

Like Twitter, you can create accounts and posts and remember them, with a limit of 140 characters, and you can see when a post is created in the past.

A shopping cart - Skills: TypeScript, JSON Website / GitHub

This is a part of an eCommerce website where a user can select each product and buy those items. Furthermore, the total price is calculated by a function.

A typing game - Skills: TypeScript, Vite, Node.js Website / GitHub

A user can type some words with keys. Then the drawing is painted by user actions and right answers. Just refresh the page to play the game again.